https://www.the-motiv.com/privacy-policy/

MOTIV PRIVACY POLICY
We recognize and respect your need for privacy and security as you visit our site. When you visit our site to view any pages, you do so without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. While we do not collect identifying information about visitors to our site, we do collect the following information for the strict purpose of tracking activity on our site:
The name of your Internet service provider. The web site that referred you to us (if any). The date and time the pages were accessed. The page or pages you requested.
There are instances where you may elect to provide us with personal information. If you fill out a feedback or request form or send us email, you are transmitting the information that appears to you in the form or the message. This will typically include information such as your name, mailing address, email address, the kind of request you are making, and any other information necessary to fulfill your request. You never transmit personally identifying information that you do not enter yourself. And this is always your option; this information cannot be collected unless you specifically elect to send it to us. This information is used internally only for the purpose of fulfilling the request or for contacting you directly and is not given or sold to any other organization.
If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at 617.263.2211.
Effective Date: 01/01/11
We reserve the right to change our privacy policy. A revised policy statement will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date. Any revisions will be posted at least 30 days prior to its effective date.
BACK TO TOP
Subscribe now!
Keep up to date with all Motiv news and announcements.
Your Name
Email
*All fields required
